<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Module on LiteGapps - Custom Google Apps Android</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/module/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Module on LiteGapps - Custom Google Apps Android</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/module/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Music Vanced Magisk Module</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/202404/music-vanced-magisk-module/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/202404/music-vanced-magisk-module/</guid>
      <description>Enhance Your Music Listening Experience with YouTube Music Vanced Magisk Module YouTube Music Vanced Magisk Module brings a new dimension to your music listening experience on Android devices. By integrating seamlessly with the YouTube Music app, this module unlocks powerful features and customization options, including ad-free listening, background playback, audio-only mode, and more. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore how this Magisk module can elevate your music streaming experience.&#xA;Features of YouTube Music Vanced Magisk Module Ad-Blocking: Tired of interruptions from ads while enjoying your favorite tunes?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Youtube Vanced Magisk Module</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/202404/youtube-vanced-magisk-module/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/202404/youtube-vanced-magisk-module/</guid>
      <description>Enhance Your YouTube Experience with YouTube Vanced Magisk Module YouTube Vanced Magisk Module is a revolutionary tool for Android users who crave a more immersive and enjoyable YouTube experience. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re tired of pesky ads interrupting your video viewing, frustrated with the inability to play videos in the background, or seeking additional customization options, this Magisk module has you covered.&#xA;What is YouTube Vanced? YouTube Vanced is a modified version of the official YouTube app that offers a plethora of features not available in the original version.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Magisk module</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/202311/best-magisk-module/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 11:02:07 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/202311/best-magisk-module/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
