<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Design on </title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/design/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Design on </description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 12:46:15 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/design/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Downhill Domination</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/game/downhill-domination/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 12:46:15 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/game/downhill-domination/</guid>
      <description>Genre: Racing Developer: Psygnosis Publisher: Infogrames (North America), SCEA (Europe) Release Date:&#xA;North America: November 19, 2002 Europe: December 6, 2002 Downhill is a fast-paced, adrenaline-pumping racing game for the PlayStation 2 (PS2) console. Developed by Psygnosis and published by Infogrames (North America) and SCEA (Europe), it was released in November 2002 (North America) and December 2002 (Europe).&#xA;Gameplay&#xA;Downhill puts players in control of mountain bikers as they race down treacherous downhill courses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WWE Smackdown Vs Raw</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/game/wwe-smackdown-vs-raw/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 12:46:15 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/game/wwe-smackdown-vs-raw/</guid>
      <description>WWE SmackDown vs. Raw was more than just a video game; it was a cultural phenomenon that captured the hearts of wrestling fans worldwide. Released for the PlayStation 2 in 2004, this title marked a turning point in the WWE gaming franchise, combining the raw energy of SmackDown with the star power of Raw.&#xA;A Match Made in Heaven Before SmackDown vs. Raw, the WWE gaming scene was divided. The SmackDown series offered a more hardcore, street-fight-oriented experience, while Raw catered to a more mainstream audience.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>God Of War 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/game/god-of-war-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 12:46:15 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/game/god-of-war-2/</guid>
      <description>God of War II is a hit hack-and-slash genre action adventure game developed by Santa Monica Studioo and published by Sony Computer Entertainment. Released for the PlayStation 2, it is the second installment in the God of War series, following the journey of Kratoss, a Spartan warrior and demigod.&#xA;Release This game was first released in North America on 14 March 2007, followed by Europe on 27 April 2006, and Australia on 4 May 2009¹².</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Final Fantasy X</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/game/final-fantasy-x/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 12:46:15 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/game/final-fantasy-x/</guid>
      <description>There seems to be some confusion! Final Fantasy 1, the original game released in 1987 for the NES, never received a port for the PlayStation 2 (PS2). The Final Fantasy series gained immense popularity on the PS2, with titles like Final Fantasy X, X-2, and XII gracing the console.&#xA;Here&amp;rsquo;s a breakdown to clear things up:&#xA;Final Fantasy 1 (1987): Released for the NES, this classic RPG laid the foundation for the series.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bully</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/game/buly/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 12:46:15 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/game/buly/</guid>
      <description>Briefly introduce the PS2 as a groundbreaking console that revolutionized gaming (release year, impact, etc.). Mention the vast library of PS2 games that cater to various genres and interests. Body&#xA;Genre-based Sections:&#xA;Action/Adventure: Highlight some of the most thrilling action-adventure games on PS2, like the beloved Grand Theft Auto series (GTA: Vice City, GTA: San Andreas), the iconic Metal Gear Solid series (Metal Gear Solid 2: Sons of Liberty, Metal Gear Solid 3: Snake Eater), and the captivating God of War.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Def Jam - Fight for NY</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/game/def-jam-fight-for-ny/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 12:46:15 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/game/def-jam-fight-for-ny/</guid>
      <description>Def Jam games on the PlayStation 2 brought the raw energy and gritty atmosphere of the hip-hop world to life. These games combined intense fighting action with a star-studded cast of real-life and fictional rappers, creating a unique and unforgettable gaming experience.&#xA;Def Jam Vendetta: A Street Fight to Remember Released in 2003, Def Jam Vendetta was the first installment in the series. It introduced players to a world of underground street fighting, where respect and reputation were everything.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fifa Street 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/game/fifa-street-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 12:46:15 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/game/fifa-street-2/</guid>
      <description>Released in 2006, FIFA Street 2 on the PlayStation 2 (PS2) built upon the success of the original FIFA Street, offering a fast-paced and flashy take on the beautiful game. Here&amp;rsquo;s a look at what made this street football title a hit:&#xA;Tricks and Flicks: FIFA Street 2 introduced a new &amp;ldquo;trick stick beat&amp;rdquo; system, giving players more control and fluidity when pulling off fancy moves. The game also boasted a wider range of authentic tricks, allowing you to recreate the skills of real-life street legends.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>God Hand</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/game/god-hand/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 12:46:15 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/game/god-hand/</guid>
      <description>Genre: Action-adventure, beat &amp;rsquo;em up&#xA;Developer: Clover Studio (Capcom)&#xA;Publisher: Capcom&#xA;Release Date: May 20, 2006 (North America)&#xA;Discontinued: Yes&#xA;Average Customer Review: 3.4 out of 5 stars (based on Amazon: amazon.com customer reviews)&#xA;Summary:&#xA;God Hand is a unique action-adventure game for the PlayStation 2 developed by Clover Studio, a former subsidiary of Capcom. The game follows the story of Gene, a clumsy yet humorous character who finds himself with a giant, divine hand grafted onto his right arm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mortal Kombat Shaolin Monks</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/game/mortal-kombat-shaolin-monks/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 12:46:15 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/game/mortal-kombat-shaolin-monks/</guid>
      <description>Mortal Kombat: Shaolin Monks, released in 2005 for the PlayStation 2, is a beat &amp;rsquo;em up action-adventure game developed by Midway Games (now NetherRealm Studios) and published by Midway Games. It&amp;rsquo;s a spin-off of the popular Mortal Kombat fighting game franchise, offering a unique perspective by allowing players to control Liu Kang and Kung Lao directly as they embark on a journey to stop the sorcerer Shang Tsung and his forces from obtaining the powerful artifacts known as the Dragon Medallions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moto GP 08</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/game/moto-gp-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 12:46:15 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/game/moto-gp-08/</guid>
      <description>MotoGP 08 is a racing video game developed by Climax Group and published by Capcom. Released in 2008, it was one of the popular titles for the PlayStation 2 console, offering fans an immersive motorcycle racing experience.&#xA;Game Overview The game accurately replicates the 2008 MotoGP season, featuring all the official riders, teams, and tracks. Players can choose to compete in various game modes, including Grand Prix, Championship, Time Trial, and Quick Race.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Naruto Shippuden Utimate Ninja 4</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/game/naruto-shippuden-utimate-ninja-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 12:46:15 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/game/naruto-shippuden-utimate-ninja-4/</guid>
      <description>Naruto Shippuden: Ultimate Ninja 4 is a fighting game developed by CyberConnect2 and published by Bandai Namco Games for the PlayStation 2. Released in March 2009, it&amp;rsquo;s part of the long-running Naruto: Ultimate Ninja series based on the popular manga and anime franchise.&#xA;Gameplay&#xA;Ultimate Ninja 4 follows the series&amp;rsquo; core mechanics of arena fighting with a focus on character jutsu (ninja techniques) and special attacks. Players choose from a roster of over 52 characters, including various versions of Naruto Uzumaki himself and his comrades and rivals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Need For Speed Most Wanted</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/game/need-for-speed-most-wanted/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 12:46:15 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/game/need-for-speed-most-wanted/</guid>
      <description>Need for Speed: Most Wanted, released in 2005 for the PlayStation 2 (PS2), is a high-octane racing game that throws you into the heart of the illicit street racing scene. Developed by EA Canada and EA Black Box, this ninth installment in the Need for Speed franchise puts you behind the wheel in a thrilling quest for revenge and racing glory.&#xA;Burn Rubber in Rockport&#xA;The fictional city of Rockport serves as your playground.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One Piece Grand Advanture</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/game/one-piece-grand-advanture/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 12:46:15 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/game/one-piece-grand-advanture/</guid>
      <description>One Piece: Grand Adventure is an action-packed video game based on the popular anime and manga series, One Piece. Released for the PlayStation 2 and GameCube in 2006, this title offers fans a thrilling adventure through the world of pirates.&#xA;Gameplay The game primarily focuses on Adventure Mode, where players embark on a quest to complete 10 levels. You&amp;rsquo;ll sail the Grand Line aboard the iconic Going Merry, visiting various islands and engaging in intense battles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pro Evolution Soccer 2011</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/game/pro-evolution-soccer-2011/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 12:46:15 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/game/pro-evolution-soccer-2011/</guid>
      <description>Pro Evolution Soccer 2011 (PES 2011) was a standout title in the beloved football gaming series, offering an immersive and engaging experience for PlayStation 2 players. Released in 2010, it captured the hearts of football fans with its realistic gameplay, strategic depth, and authentic atmosphere.&#xA;Gameplay and Features PES 2011 on PS2 showcased Konami&amp;rsquo;s commitment to refining the football gaming experience. The game featured:&#xA;Improved AI: Players exhibited more intelligent movement and decision-making, leading to more realistic and challenging matches.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rumble Racing</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/game/rumble-racing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 12:46:15 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/game/rumble-racing/</guid>
      <description>Released in 2001, Rumble Racing on the PlayStation 2 (PS2) throws players into a high-octane world of arcade racing thrills. Developed by Electronic Arts (EA) and Visceral Games, it takes inspiration from the earlier NASCAR Rumble, but with a distinct twist.&#xA;Gear Up for Wild Rides&#xA;Forget about realistic simulations. Rumble Racing is all about over-the-top action. Race across 15 wild tracks filled with jumps, ramps, hidden shortcuts, and breakable scenery.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WWE SmackDown Here Comes the Pain</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/game/wwe-smackdown-here-comes-the-pain/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 12:46:15 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/game/wwe-smackdown-here-comes-the-pain/</guid>
      <description>WWE SmackDown! Here Comes the Pain, often simply referred to as &amp;ldquo;SmackDown! Here Comes the Pain&amp;rdquo; or even just &amp;ldquo;Here Comes the Pain,&amp;rdquo; is a professional wrestling video game developed by Yuke&amp;rsquo;s and published by THQ for the PlayStation 2 console. Released in 2003, it is the fifth installment in the WWE SmackDown! series and is widely regarded as one of the best wrestling games ever made.&#xA;Gameplay&#xA;The game features a wide variety of match types, including singles matches, tag team matches, handicap matches, Royal Rumble matches, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Digimon Rumble Arena 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/game/digimon-rumble-arena-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/game/digimon-rumble-arena-2/</guid>
      <description>Digimon Rumble Arena 2 (PS2): A Nostalgic Fighting Game Experience&#xA;Digimon Rumble Arena 2, known in Japan as Digimon Battle Chronicle, is a 3D fighting game released in 2004 for the PlayStation 2, GameCube, and Xbox consoles. As a sequel to Digimon Rumble Arena, this game expanded the roster of playable Digimon, introduced new gameplay mechanics, and offered a variety of modes to keep players engaged.&#xA;Gameplay&#xA;Digimon Rumble Arena 2 features fast-paced combat with a diverse cast of Digimon characters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DragonBall Z - Budokai 3</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/game/d/dragonball-z/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/game/d/dragonball-z/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>King Arthur</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/game/k/king-arthur/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/game/k/king-arthur/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
